<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reviews on Newton Evolution Proposals (NEPs)</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/reviews/</link><description>Recent content in Reviews on Newton Evolution Proposals (NEPs)</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://neps.newtonproject.org/reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NEP Board Review 0003</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/reviews/nep-review-0003/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/reviews/nep-review-0003/</guid><description>Results # NEP No. Type Start/End Block Accepts Denies Rejects Result NEP-12 update Draft 15756530/15876529 7 0 0 Accept NEP-20 new Draft 15756497/15876496 7 0 0 Accept NEP-21 new Draft 15756503/15876502 7 0 0 Accept NEP-22 new Draft 15756508/15876507 7 0 0 Accept NEP-23 new Draft 15756516/15876515 7 0 0 Accept NEP-24 new Draft 15756523/15876522 7 0 0 Accept Details # Role Github ID NEW ADDR.</description></item><item><title>NEP Board Review 0002</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/reviews/nep-review-0002/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/reviews/nep-review-0002/</guid><description>Results # NEP No. Type Accepts Denies Rejects Final Result NEP-19 new Draft 5 0 0 Accept Details # Role Github ID NEW ADDR. NEP-19 NEP Editor @arisac NEW182LTNoiufc9tiveZdno3HXH5yEmUURKUiac new Draft NewExplorer NEP Board Member @benkoo NEW182XacauX8woduncHaXTzNGCFnk7B15z34hi NEP Board Member @evanliuchina NEW182Jqu3ok6ZnjkLAyhpSw9WEJXhEwUYX4jLR NEP Board Member @i29 NEW182TpZToiXBk1SkR1bMJLUxguPxFsZciz123 Accept NewExplorer NEP Board Member @jiangtao-tang NEW182XmN8jkgnkW8rtu9jRriQJjnEBXSbZZuHJ Accept NewExplorer NEP Board Member @leewillson NEW182ZheiEbSBW3SbtETmXEgdG5X9GvFuLRun2 Accept NewExplorer NEP Board Member @VieYang NEW182bMUiAM1nXMjcwri8zNrgZftcnPJc1uVie Accept NewExplorer NEP Board Member @xiawu NEW182Kt8siZGciPGBss3rg7GmJqfZ7CUafVUHH NEP Board Member @xujizhe unregistered NEP Board Member @zqy15789 NEW182EFjxZjxRJcfBdJBHEuMTYNsK7RLTFeiiJ Accept NewExplorer Notice # Voting Period: 2020-06-04 12:00 UTC+8 to 2020-06-05 13:00 UTC+8</description></item><item><title>NEP Board Review 0001</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/reviews/nep-review-0001/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/reviews/nep-review-0001/</guid><description>Results # NEP No. Type Accepts Denies Rejects Final Result NEP-6 new Draft 6 0 0 Accept NEP-7 new Draft 6 0 0 Accept NEP-10 new Draft 6 0 0 Accept NEP-12 new Draft 5 0 0 Accept Details # Role Github ID NEW ADDR. NEP-6 NEP-7 NEP-10 NEP-12 NEP Editor @arisac NEW182LTNoiufc9tiveZdno3HXH5yEmUURKUiac new Draft View on NewExplorer new Draft View on NewExplorer NEP Editor @liuyong5653 NEW182VbmZs3TyC268wz7Kq4Cznssv7WzRPDq7j new Draft View on NewExplorer NEP Editor @weixuefeng NEW182PdJBJoMnGAub6KJ6YrhSPHWrFE9RSBmGE new Draft View on NewExplorer NEP Board Member @benkoo NEW182XacauX8woduncHaXTzNGCFnk7B15z34hi NEP Board Member @evanliuchina NEW182Jqu3ok6ZnjkLAyhpSw9WEJXhEwUYX4jLR Accept View on NewExplorer Accept View on NewExplorer Accept View on NewExplorer Accept View on NewExplorer NEP Board Member @i29 NEW182TpZToiXBk1SkR1bMJLUxguPxFsZciz123 Accept View on NewExplorer Accept View on NewExplorer Accept View on NewExplorer Accept View on NewExplorer NEP Board Member @jiangtao-tang NEW182XmN8jkgnkW8rtu9jRriQJjnEBXSbZZuHJ Accept View on NewExplorer Accept View on NewExplorer Accept View on NewExplorer Accept View on NewExplorer NEP Board Member @leewillson NEW182ZheiEbSBW3SbtETmXEgdG5X9GvFuLRun2 Accept View on NewExplorer Accept View on NewExplorer Accept View on NewExplorer Accept View on NewExplorer NEP Board Member @VieYang NEW182bMUiAM1nXMjcwri8zNrgZftcnPJc1uVie Accept View on NewExplorer Accept View on NewExplorer Accept View on NewExplorer Accept View on NewExplorer NEP Board Member @xiawu NEW182Kt8siZGciPGBss3rg7GmJqfZ7CUafVUHH NEP Board Member @xujizhe unregistered NEP Board Member @zqy15789 NEW182EFjxZjxRJcfBdJBHEuMTYNsK7RLTFeiiJ Accept View on NewExplorer Accept View on NewExplorer Accept View on NewExplorer Notice # Voting Period: 2020-05-08 12:00 UTC+8 to 2020-05-09 12:00 UTC+8</description></item></channel></rss>