<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Implemented on Newton Evolution Proposals (NEPs)</title><link>https://neps.newton.bio/status/implemented/</link><description>Recent content in Implemented on Newton Evolution Proposals (NEPs)</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://neps.newton.bio/status/implemented/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Boom: EVM and Protocol Upgrades</title><link>https://neps.newton.bio/neps/nep-26/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newton.bio/neps/nep-26/</guid><description>Simple Summary # Enable the outstanding Ethereum Foundation Constantinople, St. Petersburg and Istanbul network protocol upgrades on the NewChain network in a hard-fork code-named Boom to enable maximum compatibility across these networks.
Abstract # Add support for a subset of protocol-impacting changes introduced in the Ethereum Foundation (ETH) network via the Constantinople, St. Petersburg and Istanbul hardforks. The proposed changes for NewChain&amp;rsquo;s Boom upgrade include:
Bitwise shifting instructions in EVM Skinny CREATE2 EXTCODEHASH opcode Net gas metering for SSTORE without dirty maps Add Blake2 compression function F precompile Reduce alt_bn128 precompile gas costs Add ChainID opcode Repricing for trie-size-dependent opcodes Calldata gas cost reduction Rebalance net-metered SSTORE gas cost with consideration of SLOAD gas cost change This document proposes the following blocks at which to implement these changes in the NewChain networks:</description></item><item><title>Improvement to Newton Foundation Reserved Token Release Rules</title><link>https://neps.newton.bio/neps/nep-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newton.bio/neps/nep-1/</guid><description>Summary: # In order to ensure the scarcity and reasonable liquidity of Newton tokens (NEW), based on the ideas and opinions of all parties, the following suggestions are put forth to modify the token release rules.
Details: # The plan for Newton Foundation reserved token release as stated in the Newton White Paper V0.5 is that “1/2 of the total is immediately unlocked, while the rest will be unlocked 1/12 every month.</description></item><item><title>NEP Genesis</title><link>https://neps.newton.bio/neps/nep-0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newton.bio/neps/nep-0/</guid><description>Summary: # For the sake of the open, transparent governance, we propose compiling all suggestions related to the Newton Project using the Newton Evolution Proposal (NEP) template for unified numbering and management. The proposals are then put to the community for broader discussion, getting opinions and suggestions from all parties involved before forming final conclusions.
Details: # Anyone can submit an NEP. The Newton Foundation is responsible for assigning an exclusive number to each.</description></item></channel></rss>