<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Community Governance on Newton Evolution Proposals (NEPs)</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/categories/community-governance/</link><description>Recent content in Community Governance on Newton Evolution Proposals (NEPs)</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://neps.newtonproject.org/categories/community-governance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Change On Community NEW Release Plan</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-40/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-40/</guid><description>Simple Summary # To advance the NewChain development, the original NEW release plan of the community (60% of 100B total supply) will be changed as described below.
Abstract # The total supply of NEW is 100B, 60% of which is subjected to the community.
It can be divided into three parts as below:
already released: 1545232707.3505096555 NEW 2021/2/1-2022/1/31 for incentives: 875130267.8946381786 NEW the rest: 57579637024.7548521659 NEW (will be decided by the future community governance) The seconds part will be used for supporting the Newton Incentive Program.</description></item><item><title>NEP Genesis</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-0/</guid><description>Summary: # For the sake of the open, transparent governance, we propose compiling all suggestions related to the Newton Project using the Newton Evolution Proposal (NEP) template for unified numbering and management. The proposals are then put to the community for broader discussion, getting opinions and suggestions from all parties involved before forming final conclusions.
Details: # Anyone can submit an NEP. The Newton Foundation is responsible for assigning an exclusive number to each.</description></item><item><title>NewChain MainNet Opening</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-27/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-27/</guid><description>Simple Summary # After NewChain TestNet successful opening, NewChain MainNet is going to be opened by inviting the community to setup, run and maintain the ledger nodes.
Abstract # In current stage, NewChain MainNet would still run with PoA (Proof-of-Authority) consensus mechanism for producing blocks. Hence a certain amount of staking would be required for keeping the ledger nodes honest and not be malicious to harm the network.</description></item><item><title>NewPay Community Node Migration</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-29/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-29/</guid><description>Simple Summary # As part of the NewChain MainNet opening strategy and upgrading plan, the current &amp;ldquo;community nodes&amp;rdquo; in NewPay for virtual mining would be migrated and resolved for paving the way of NewChain to embrace a more bright future.
This proposal will illustrate a possible solution for migrating them to be integrated into the NewSwap mining framework to also benefit the development of NewSwap.
Abstract # The current &amp;ldquo;community nodes&amp;rdquo; in NewPay are doing &amp;ldquo;virtual mining&amp;rdquo; nowadays for daily released NEW from NewPool.</description></item></channel></rss>