<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Community Governance on Newton Evolution Proposals (NEPs)</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/categories/community-governance/</link><description>Recent content in Community Governance on Newton Evolution Proposals (NEPs)</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://neps.newtonproject.org/categories/community-governance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Change On Community NEW Budget Plan</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-40/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-40/</guid><description>Simple Summary # To advance the NewChain development, the budget plan of the NEW release for the community (60% of 100B total supply) will be changed as described below. The release plan and curve will be the same as established.
Motivation # Newton has a release plan of 60B NEW to help the community develop. Since the project launched, the released NEW has been allocated to only one project, the current NewPay Community Node mining (Proof-of-Stake).</description></item><item><title>Change On Community Node NEW Unlocking Period</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-43/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-43/</guid><description>Simple Summary # This proposal changes the Community Node NEW unlocking period from 14 days to 7 days for owners and partners to unlock their staked NEW. Making the unlocking period the same as voters to unlock their staked NEW.
Abstract # In NewPay App, unlock NEW for Community Node owners/partners from their staked NEW will be changed from 14 days to 7 days to help them to get their NEW back faster.</description></item><item><title>NEP Genesis</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-0/</guid><description>Summary: # For the sake of the open, transparent governance, we propose compiling all suggestions related to the Newton Project using the Newton Evolution Proposal (NEP) template for unified numbering and management. The proposals are then put to the community for broader discussion, getting opinions and suggestions from all parties involved before forming final conclusions.
Details: # Anyone can submit an NEP. The Newton Foundation is responsible for assigning an exclusive number to each.</description></item><item><title>NewChain Ledger Node Incentive Program</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-45/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-45/</guid><description>Simple Summary # This NEP defines how NewChain Ledger Node Incentive is used from Newton Incentive Program in NEP-40.
Motivation # NEP-40 proposed Newton Incentive Program and a 20% of NEW from that program will be used to NewChain Ledger Nodes. A specification of implementation is required for that, which comes to this NewChain Ledger Node Incentive Program.
Specification # Prerequisites for Ledger Node # Having an active Community Node.</description></item><item><title>NewChain MainNet Opening</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-27/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-27/</guid><description>Simple Summary # After NewChain TestNet successful opening, NewChain MainNet is going to be opened by inviting the community to setup, run and maintain the ledger nodes.
Abstract # In current stage, NewChain MainNet would still run with PoA (Proof-of-Authority) consensus mechanism for producing blocks. Hence a certain amount of staking would be required for keeping the ledger nodes honest and not be malicious to harm the network.</description></item><item><title>NewPay Community Node Migration</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-29/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-29/</guid><description>Simple Summary # As part of the NewChain MainNet opening strategy and upgrading plan, the current &amp;ldquo;community nodes&amp;rdquo; in NewPay for virtual mining would be migrated and resolved for paving the way of NewChain to embrace a more bright future.
This proposal will illustrate a possible solution for migrating them to be integrated into the NewSwap mining framework to also benefit the development of NewSwap.
Abstract # The current &amp;ldquo;community nodes&amp;rdquo; in NewPay are doing &amp;ldquo;virtual mining&amp;rdquo; nowadays for daily released NEW from NewPool.</description></item><item><title>Parameter Updates on Community Node and vote</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-47/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-47/</guid><description>Simple Summary # This proposal contains parameter changes on community node mining, including NEW staking period, mining reward calculation, and minumam lock amount.
Abstract # Changes on NewPay:
Change NEW staking period on community node and vote. Change minumam lock amount on community node and vote to 10000 NEW. Change community node NF factor to 1, same as community vote NF factor. Motivation # NewChain MainNet ledger nodes are open to public since NEP-27 has been implemented.</description></item></channel></rss>