<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>NEPs Guidelines on Newton Evolution Proposals (NEPs)</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/guides/</link><description>Recent content in NEPs Guidelines on Newton Evolution Proposals (NEPs)</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://neps.newtonproject.org/guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contributing a NEP</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/guides/contributing-a-nep/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/guides/contributing-a-nep/</guid><description>This doc was originally from https://github.com/newtonproject/NEPs/wiki and should be added to a NEP as reference. Review NEP-0 and guidelines in this document. Fork the repository by clicking &amp;ldquo;Fork&amp;rdquo; in the top right. Add your NEP to your fork of the repository. Use a template to start your NEP. Submit a Pull Request to Newton&amp;rsquo;s NEPs repository. Start A NEP # We welcome anyone with suggestions related to Newton Project to compile a NEP.</description></item><item><title>NEP Submission Guides for Beginners</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/guides/nep-submission-guide-for-beginners/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/guides/nep-submission-guide-for-beginners/</guid><description>This doc was originally from https://github.com/newtonproject/NEPs/wiki and should be added to a NEP as reference. This guide is for those unfamiliar with the NEP Process and provides simple instructions for NEP submission, update, and request for final. This guide won&amp;rsquo;t cover complex NEP status change and other requests described in NEPs Guideline.
This guide covers:
Start A NEP
To Submit NEP for The First Time</description></item><item><title>NEP Process</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/guides/nep-process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/guides/nep-process/</guid><description>This doc was originally from https://github.com/newtonproject/NEPs/wiki and should be added to a NEP as reference. Shepherding a NEP # Parties &amp;amp; Roles involved in the process a NEP are: NEP you, the NEP Champion(Lead) or Authors, NEP Editors, NEP Review Board, and the Public Communnity.
Before you begin writing a formal NEP, you should vet your idea. Ask the Newton community first if an idea is original to avoid wasting time on something that will be be rejected based on prior research.</description></item><item><title>NEP Status</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/guides/nep-status/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/guides/nep-status/</guid><description>This doc was originally from https://github.com/newtonproject/NEPs/wiki and should be added to a NEP as reference. I. Available NEP Statuses # Statuses listed below is the Standard NEP Status for Newton Evolution Proposals.
Regular Statuses # WIP Draft Public Call Final Implemented Special Statuses # Deferred Superseded Active Abandoned Rejected II. Status Definations # Each status change is requested by the NEP author and reviewed by the NEP editors.</description></item><item><title>NEP Editors</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/guides/nep-editors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/guides/nep-editors/</guid><description>This doc was originally from https://github.com/newtonproject/NEPs/wiki and should be added to a NEP as reference. NEP Editors Responsibilities # For each new NEP that comes in, an editor does the following:
Read the NEP to check if it is ready: sound and complete. The ideas must make technical sense, even if they don&amp;rsquo;t seem likely to get to final status. The title should accurately describe the content. Check the NEP for language (spelling, grammar, sentence structure, etc.</description></item><item><title>Review Board</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/guides/nep-review-board/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/guides/nep-review-board/</guid><description>This doc was originally from https://github.com/newtonproject/NEPs/wiki and should be added to a NEP as reference. Current Review Board Members # Display Name GitHub ID NEW Address Mr. Koo @benkoo NEW182XacauX8woduncHaXTzNGCFnk7B15z34hi Evan Liu @evanliuchina NEW182Jqu3ok6ZnjkLAyhpSw9WEJXhEwUYX4jLR Qu Jianwei @i29 NEW182TpZToiXBk1SkR1bMJLUxguPxFsZciz123 Jiang Tao @jiangtao-tang NEW182XmN8jkgnkW8rtu9jRriQJjnEBXSbZZuHJ Lee Willson @leewillson NEW182ZheiEbSBW3SbtETmXEgdG5X9GvFuLRun2 VieYang @VieYang NEW182bMUiAM1nXMjcwri8zNrgZftcnPJc1uVie xiawu @xiawu NEW182Kt8siZGciPGBss3rg7GmJqfZ7CUafVUHH Xu Jizhe @xujizhe unregistered zqy15789 @zqy15789 NEW182EFjxZjxRJcfBdJBHEuMTYNsK7RLTFeiiJ</description></item><item><title>Transferring NEP Ownership</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/guides/transfer-nep-ownership/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/guides/transfer-nep-ownership/</guid><description>This doc was originally from https://github.com/newtonproject/NEPs/wiki and should be added to a NEP as reference. It occasionally becomes necessary to transfer ownership of NEPs to a new champion. In general, we’d like to retain the original author as a co-author of the transferred NEP, but that’s really up to the original author. A good reason to transfer ownership is because the original author no longer has the time or interest in updating it or following through with the NEP process, or has fallen off the face of the net (i.</description></item></channel></rss>