<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Process on Newton Evolution Proposals (NEPs)</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/types/process/</link><description>Recent content in Process on Newton Evolution Proposals (NEPs)</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://neps.newtonproject.org/types/process/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Boom: EVM and Protocol Upgrades</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-26/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-26/</guid><description>Simple Summary # Enable the outstanding Ethereum Foundation Constantinople, St. Petersburg and Istanbul network protocol upgrades on the NewChain network in a hard-fork code-named Boom to enable maximum compatibility across these networks.
Abstract # Add support for a subset of protocol-impacting changes introduced in the Ethereum Foundation (ETH) network via the Constantinople, St. Petersburg and Istanbul hardforks. The proposed changes for NewChain&amp;rsquo;s Boom upgrade include:
Bitwise shifting instructions in EVM Skinny CREATE2 EXTCODEHASH opcode Net gas metering for SSTORE without dirty maps Add Blake2 compression function F precompile Reduce alt_bn128 precompile gas costs Add ChainID opcode Repricing for trie-size-dependent opcodes Calldata gas cost reduction Rebalance net-metered SSTORE gas cost with consideration of SLOAD gas cost change This document proposes the following blocks at which to implement these changes in the NewChain networks:</description></item><item><title>Change On Community NEW Release Plan</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-40/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-40/</guid><description>Simple Summary # To advance the NewChain development, the original NEW release plan of the community (60% of 100B total supply) will be changed as described below.
Abstract # The total supply of NEW is 100B, 60% of which is subjected to the community.
It can be divided into three parts as below:
already released: 1545232707.3505096555 NEW 2021/2/1-2022/1/31 for incentives: 875130267.8946381786 NEW the rest: 57579637024.7548521659 NEW (will be decided by the future community governance) The seconds part will be used for supporting the Newton Incentive Program.</description></item><item><title>NewChain MainNet Opening</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-27/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-27/</guid><description>Simple Summary # After NewChain TestNet successful opening, NewChain MainNet is going to be opened by inviting the community to setup, run and maintain the ledger nodes.
Abstract # In current stage, NewChain MainNet would still run with PoA (Proof-of-Authority) consensus mechanism for producing blocks. Hence a certain amount of staking would be required for keeping the ledger nodes honest and not be malicious to harm the network.</description></item><item><title>NewPay Community Node Migration</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-29/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-29/</guid><description>Simple Summary # As part of the NewChain MainNet opening strategy and upgrading plan, the current &amp;ldquo;community nodes&amp;rdquo; in NewPay for virtual mining would be migrated and resolved for paving the way of NewChain to embrace a more bright future.
This proposal will illustrate a possible solution for migrating them to be integrated into the NewSwap mining framework to also benefit the development of NewSwap.
Abstract # The current &amp;ldquo;community nodes&amp;rdquo; in NewPay are doing &amp;ldquo;virtual mining&amp;rdquo; nowadays for daily released NEW from NewPool.</description></item></channel></rss>