<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Standard on Newton Evolution Proposals (NEPs)</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/types/standard/</link><description>Recent content in Standard on Newton Evolution Proposals (NEPs)</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://neps.newtonproject.org/types/standard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NEAT Backed Currency (NBC)</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-23/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-23/</guid><description>Simple Summary # NEAT Backed Currency (NBC) is a kind of cryptographically secured currency following the design protocol of NEAT. The goal of this creation is the allow anyone to create a set of exchangeable, and divisible asset that can be securely exchanged using the platform provided by Newton Community. We used the term community, because the distributed security, must be backed by a community of infrastructure providers and a rather healthy exchange community.</description></item><item><title>Newton Composite Asset (NCA)</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-22/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-22/</guid><description>Simple Summary # Newton Composite Asset (NCA) is the base pattern of asset combination that defines the boundary of how two or more than two assets are combined as a single instance. NCA distinguishes from the other types of asset by involving more than one NEAT. Every NCA is defined based on the principle of Behavioral Equivalence 1, so that unique properties of NCA can be distinguished computationally and therefore maximize the possibility of code reuse and automated asset valuation.</description></item><item><title>Newton Encoded Asset Transaction (NEAT)</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-20/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-20/</guid><description>Simple Summary # Newton Encoded Asset Transaction(NEAT) defines the root data type for all asset exchanges. Once a new record of NEAT is registered into Newchain, it represents a form of irrefutable accountability based on the immutable features of Newchain. To help transaction assess the worthiness of transactions before their commitment, all transactions have a common field, called: Bounded Accountability, which defines all known exit conditions when a transactional process is breached.</description></item><item><title>Newton Physical Asset (NPA)</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-21/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-21/</guid><description>Simple Summary # Newton Physical Asset (NPA) is the base class of physical asset classes. NPA requires certain proof mechanisms to be included as a part of guarantee to allow transaction of ownership. Two basic types of proof must be made available:
Proof of Existence: The asset must provide some mechanism to show the asset exists, such as some online API to show that certain goods or services physically exist, that responded with some provable existence message.</description></item><item><title>Newton Pre-paid Card (NPC)</title><link>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-24/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neps.newtonproject.org/neps/nep-24/</guid><description>Simple Summary # Newton Pre-paid Card (NPC) is a cryptographically insured asset that works with exchangeable assets within the Newton Community. It can be extended to issue Membership Card, Score Cards, or even Balanced Score Cards. It can also possess negotiating powers in attaining tangible goods. For example, one may pre-pay for editable goods, such as vegetable, milk, or beef, or other kinds of commercially viable goods. The basic assumptions about NPC is that it provides a classification scheme to define goods.</description></item></channel></rss>